<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  ~ Copyright (c) 2018, Olga Agafonova. All Rights Reserved.
  -->
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Inhale</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="inhale">Inhale</string>
    <string name="exhale">Exhale</string>
    <string name="breathe">Breathe normally</string>
    <string name="tv_exercisemode_text">"4 seconds : 2 seconds"</string>
    <string name="button_length">Length</string>
    <string name="button_stopStart">Start</string>
    <string name="placeholder" translatable="false">"00:00:00"</string>
    <string name="exhalation_inhalation">"Exhalation : Inhalation"</string>
    <string name="exhale_4">"4 seconds"</string>
    <string name="exhale_6">"6 seconds"</string>
    <string name="exhale_8">"8 seconds"</string>
    <string name="exhale_10">"10 seconds"</string>
    <string name="exhale_12">"12 seconds"</string>
    <string name="inhale_2">"2 seconds"</string>
    <string name="inhale_3">"3 seconds"</string>
    <string name="inhale_4">"4 seconds"</string>
    <string name="inhale_5">"5 seconds"</string>
    <string name="inhale_6">"6 seconds"</string>
    <string name="important">Important: do not exceed your comfort level.</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="copyright_label">Copyright Notice</string>
    <string name="copyright_notice">Copyright (c) 2018, Olga Agafonova. All rights reserved.</string>
    <string name="music_label">Music License</string>
    <string name="music_notice">Soundtrack \"Snowburn-Instrumental\" by Hammock. Licensed through the Music Bed, LLC.</string>
    <string name="disclaimer">Disclaimer</string>
    <string name="fitness_disclaimer">Fitness Disclaimer</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_text">The information contained on Inhale mobile app (the \"Service\") is
        for general information purposes only. \n \n

        Inhale assumes no responsibility for errors or omissions in the contents on the Service. \n \n

        In no event shall Inhale be liable for any special, direct, indirect, consequential, or incidental
        damages or any damages whatsoever, whether in an action of contract, negligence or other tort,
        arising out of or in connection with the use of the Service or the contents of the Service.
        Inhale reserves the right to make additions, deletions, or modification to the contents on
        the Service at any time without prior notice.
    </string>
    <string name="fitness_disclaimer_text">The Service offers health, fitness and nutritional information
        and is designed for educational purposes only. You should not rely on this information
        as a substitute for, nor does it replace, professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment.
        If you have any concerns or questions about your health, you should always consult with a
        physician or other health-care professional. \n \n

        Do not disregard, avoid or delay obtaining medical or health related advice from
        your health-care professional because of something you may have read on the Service.
        The use of any information provided on the Service is solely at your own risk.
    </string>
</resources>
